<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OneMoreChance</string>
    <string name="language">Please select language</string>
    <string name="idioma">Por Favor Seleccionar Idioma</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">Info</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_results">SearchResults</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_event_to_calendar">AddEventToCalendar</string>
    <string name="title_activity_program_info">ProgramInfo</string>
    <string name="description">I have been alone with you inside my mind
And in my dreams I have kissed your lips a thousand times
I sometimes see you pass outside my door
Hello, is it me you are looking for?

I can see it in your eyes
I can see it in your smile
You are all I have ever wanted, and my arms are open wide
because you know just what to say
And you know just what to do
And I want to tell you so much, I love you

I long to see the sunlight in your hair
And tell you time and time again how much I care
Sometimes I feel my heart will overflow
Hello, I have just got to let you know

because I wonder where you are
And I wonder what you do
Are you somewhere feeling lonely, or is someone loving you?
Tell me how to win your heart
For I haven not got a clue
But let me start by saying, I love you
 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_practice">practice</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="zip_code">Zip Code</string>
    <string name="advanced_search">Advanced Search</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="citizenship_status">Citizenship Status</string>
    <string name="new_event_title">Title</string>
    <string name="event_title_description">Write the title to your new event</string>
    <string name="location">Write the location to the event here.</string>
    <string name="location_title">Location</string>
    <string name="descriotion">Write your description</string>
    <string name="description_title">Description</string>
    <string name="create_event">Create Event</string>
    <string name="undocumented">Undocumented</string>
    <string name="immigrant">Immigrants</string>
    <string name="refrugees">Refugees</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="preferred_program_language">Preferred program language</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="new_search">New Search</string>
    <string name="search_result">Search Results</string>
    <string name="give_feedback_on_appointment">Give feedback on appointment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_biography_class">BiographyClass</string>
    <string name="bio_elvis">I was born in Brooklyn New York, but when I was a year old my mother
        brought me to the Dominican Republic. I took the decision to come to United State when I was
        20 years old. When I came here I did not know English at all, my aunt told me about a free
        English class that they offered in a school near by where I used to live; from there I went
        to college and started taking ESL classes; however, I had to wait for a whole year to take
        financial aid because I was not a resident of New York City long enough to qualify for
        Financial aid. I waste few months because I did not know anything of how the system work
        here at the United State. I was not working at the time and my cousin told me to apply for
        SNAP that way I could help my brother with at least the food. If it was not for my family I
        would not know about the benefits of this country</string>

    <string name="spanol_bio_elvis">
        Yo nací en Brooklyn New York, pero cuando tenia un año de edad mi madre me llevo para la
        República Dominicana. Yo tomé la decisión de venir para los Estados Unidos cuando tenía 20
        años de edad. Cuando yo vine para este país no sabía nada de Ingles, mi tía me dijo de un
        programa gratuito de Ingles en una escuela que estaba cerca de donde yo vivía; después de
        ahi yo fui para la universidad donde empece a tomar clases de Ingles como Segunda Lengua;
        sin embargo, yo tube que esperar un año completo para poder recibir la ayuda financiera
        porque yo no era residente de la ciudad de Nueva York el tiempo requerido para calificar.
        Yo desperdicie algunos meses porque no sabia nada de como funcionaba el sistema aquí en los
        Estados Unidos. No estaba trabajando cuando recién llegue y un primo me dijo que aplicara
        para los cupones de comida, de esa manera podría ayudar a mi hermano por lo menos con la
        comida. Si no hubiese sido por mi familia nunca hubiese sabido acerca de los beneficios de
        este país. </string>


</resources>
